God is still saying something.
Holy Spirit, we thank You.
Give thanks to God.
Give thanks to Him.
I want us to lift up our voice and pray this
coming Thursday.
Whatever that will happen that will cause
a conflict between the superpower nations.
Because I see a situation where one will tempt the other and that will provoke the whole thing
This coming Thursday.
Please, raise up your voice and begin to pray.
Pray that God should hold their temper, no
matter the temptation from the other side,
to another country.
The other country they tempted should hold
its temper - and should not be provoked to retaliate.
Then, if they retaliate - well, me and you
- our fate is hung.
Raise up your hand.
This coming Thursday, Friday - pray that whatever
that will happen that will cause any nation,
one of the super-nations to be provoked, to
retaliate - the Lord should hold their temper.
No matter what happens, hold your temper.
Father, You are the Lord that created all things.
You can loose, You can bind.
Whatever that will happen this coming Thursday
and Friday, that will cause other nations
to be tempted to lose their temper...
If one is tempted, it's attack.
And the other may lose their temper; that
is it.
Father, hold their temper.
Let them be calm; we ask for calmness.
We ask for calmness, in the name of Jesus
Christ!
This is what I saw in 2015 and 2016.
I said, "The fight in Syria will provoke other
fights."
They are playing it now and I said, "The Lord
should save us."
I was crying.
This coming Thursday and Friday are key days.
Please fast from morning until 12 midday.
I know all the nations and people that watch
Emmanuel TV.
When it happens, they will say, 'Ah, this
man said we should hold our temper'.
For the sake of peace, for the sake of harmony
in the world.
What is on the ground now is a devil's workshop.
The foundation for a devil's workshop is on
the ground.
We are talking of economic meltdown but another
one entirely.
With what is happening now, we cannot talk
of economic meltdown.
Whatever you see, you should eat it and talk
about your safety.
That is it.
We continue to pray, since God has shown us.
We will see; God will intervene.